[{"problem":"NKTOSS","solution":"http://simizer.com/tFy","link":"http://simizer.com/A4O"},
    {"problem":"QTREEX","solution":"http://simizer.com/tCy","link":"http://simizer.com/A6V"},
    {"problem":"CHAIN2","solution":"http://simizer.com/EaT","link":"http://simizer.com/sl4"},
    {"problem":"QTREE","solution":"http://simizer.com/1EY","link":"http://simizer.com/1II"},
    {"problem":"QTREE5","solution":"http://simizer.com/F4Q","link":"http://simizer.com/DoM"},
    {"problem":"DHLOCO","solution":"http://simizer.com/SPF","link":"http://simizer.com/QP0"},
    {"problem":"METERAIN","solution":"http://simizer.com/SOh","link":"http://simizer.com/OCo"},
    {"problem":"AUCTION","solution":"http://simizer.com/aQi","link":"http://simizer.com/aLy"},
    {"problem":"KDIFF","solution":"http://simizer.com/c1v","link":"http://simizer.com/c2j"},
    {"problem":"LEM4","solution":"http://simizer.com/VxY","link":"http://simizer.com/Vha"},
    {"problem":"LUBENICA","solution":"http://simizer.com/T0f","link":"http://simizer.com/T82"},
    {"problem":"QVESCAPE","solution":"http://simizer.com/T7S","link":"http://simizer.com/Snm"},
    {"problem":"XUCXAC","solution":"http://simizer.com/tJI","link":"http://simizer.com/Smx"},
    {"problem":"BONUS","solution":"http://simizer.com/Q22","link":"http://simizer.com/PiD"},
    {"problem":"VOLIS","solution":"http://simizer.com/szz","link":"http://simizer.com/ROJ"},
    {"problem":"UPGRANET","solution":"http://simizer.com/a5N","link":"http://simizer.com/SoC"},
    {"problem":"C11CAL","solution":"http://simizer.com/eKO","link":"http://simizer.com/eKw"},
    {"problem":"ETF","solution":"http://simizer.com/eoe","link":"http://simizer.com/ep6"},
    {"problem":"JEWELNB","solution":"http://simizer.com/trY","link":"http://simizer.com/tYn"},
    {"problem":"KVIP","solution":"http://simizer.com/egq","link":"http://simizer.com/ehT"},
    {"problem":"LATGACH4","solution":"http://simizer.com/eyK","link":"http://simizer.com/ezN"},
    {"problem":"LEM3","solution":"http://simizer.com/o2c","link":"http://simizer.com/o00"},
    {"problem":"LQDRACE","solution":"http://simizer.com/svb","link":"http://simizer.com/t0W"},
    {"problem":"MIXUP2","solution":"http://simizer.com/n5Y","link":"http://simizer.com/n8t"},
    {"problem":"NUCLEAR","solution":"http://simizer.com/nhx","link":"http://simizer.com/npX"},
    {"problem":"PERREC","solution":"http://simizer.com/tLj","link":"http://simizer.com/olO"},
    {"problem":"QBSCHOOL","solution":"http://simizer.com/yzz","link":"http://simizer.com/z3L"},
    {"problem":"QTREEV","solution":"http://simizer.com/tPS","link":"http://simizer.com/pL2"},
    {"problem":"VOTREE","solution":"http://simizer.com/w59","link":"http://simizer.com/w8B"},
    {"problem":"WEATHER","solution":"http://simizer.com/s2r","link":"http://simizer.com/rrG"},
    {"problem":"ADS","solution":"http://dataurbia.com/2uq","link":"http://dataurbia.com/32f"},
    {"problem":"BINARY","solution":"http://simizer.com/uaT","link":"http://simizer.com/ubX"},
    {"problem":"CHAIN","solution":"http://simizer.com/vNo","link":"http://simizer.com/vYb"},
    {"problem":"KPLANK","solution":"http://simizer.com/191D","link":"http://simizer.com/18vT"},
    {"problem":"LEM5","solution":"http://dataurbia.com/ZI","link":"http://dataurbia.com/Zr"},
    {"problem":"MILITARY","solution":"http://dataurbia.com/3ww","link":"http://dataurbia.com/3pY"},
    {"problem":"MINROAD","solution":"http://simizer.com/18oC","link":"http://simizer.com/18jF"},
    {"problem":"NETACCEL","solution":"http://simizer.com/qKV","link":"http://simizer.com/qJk"},
    {"problem":"PBCDEM","solution":"http://simizer.com/q8H","link":"http://simizer.com/q9D"},
    {"problem":"PERIODNB","solution":"http://dataurbia.com/3Td","link":"http://dataurbia.com/3KF"},
    {"problem":"QBPAL","solution":"http://dataurbia.com/3OO","link":"http://dataurbia.com/3PP"},
    {"problem":"RELINETS","solution":"http://dataurbia.com/5x3","link":"http://dataurbia.com/5y8"},
    {"problem":"VMSUBSTR","solution":"http://dataurbia.com/yd","link":"http://dataurbia.com/10E"},
    {"problem":"BARICAVN","solution":"http://dataurbia.com/Pso","link":"http://dataurbia.com/PTm"},
    {"problem":"COND","solution":"http://dataurbia.com/GBa","link":"http://dataurbia.com/G5t"},
    {"problem":"IOIBIN","solution":"http://dataurbia.com/OqS","link":"http://dataurbia.com/PBz"},
    {"problem":"KMEDIAN","solution":"http://dataurbia.com/R2F","link":"http://dataurbia.com/Ql0"},
    {"problem":"KQUERY","solution":"http://dataurbia.com/2pH","link":"http://dataurbia.com/2sa"},
    {"problem":"MROADS","solution":"http://dataurbia.com/Pgu","link":"http://dataurbia.com/PEA"},
    {"problem":"NETWRKNB","solution":"http://dataurbia.com/Kt8","link":"http://dataurbia.com/Kwp"},
    {"problem":"NKLEAVES","solution":"http://dataurbia.com/FDh","link":"http://dataurbia.com/FEF"},
    {"problem":"NKPOS","solution":"http://dataurbia.com/KU1","link":"http://dataurbia.com/KRi"},
    {"problem":"QBBUILD","solution":"http://dataurbia.com/PUB","link":"http://dataurbia.com/PQd"},
    {"problem":"QBDIVSEQ","solution":"http://dataurbia.com/RDH","link":"http://dataurbia.com/RF0"},
    {"problem":"QBGAME","solution":"http://dataurbia.com/KVD","link":"http://dataurbia.com/KQQ"},
    {"problem":"VECTOR","solution":"http://dataurbia.com/Flk","link":"http://dataurbia.com/Fkv"},
    {"problem":"VMRR","solution":"http://dataurbia.com/R4q","link":"http://dataurbia.com/R5Q"},
    {"problem":"VO17TV","solution":"http://dataurbia.com/RUB","link":"http://dataurbia.com/RUb"},
    {"problem":"INCSEQ","solution":"http://dataurbia.com/f8E","link":"http://dataurbia.com/f8q"},
    {"problem":"INCVN","solution":"http://adf.ly/1ni7cn","link":"http://adf.ly/1ni6lP"},
    {"problem":"INTEGER7","solution":"http://dataurbia.com/iKQ","link":"http://dataurbia.com/iJF"},
    {"problem":"QTSEQ","solution":"http://dataurbia.com/mao","link":"http://ideone.com/BNYqU2"},
    {"problem":"QUEENNB","solution":"http://dataurbia.com/m5H","link":"http://dataurbia.com/lxG"},
    {"problem":"RBULL","solution":"http://dataurbia.com/dNm","link":"http://dataurbia.com/dQa"},
    {"problem":"VMDAOBIT","solution":"http://dataurbia.com/dmF","link":"http://dataurbia.com/dmd"},
    {"problem":"VMRESTO","solution":"http://dataurbia.com/i8f","link":"http://dataurbia.com/i9B"},
    {"problem":"BGMINE","solution":"http://dataurbia.com/11Ky","link":"http://dataurbia.com/17qS"},
    {"problem":"C11BC2","solution":"http://dataurbia.com/14qk","link":"http://dataurbia.com/14r5"},
    {"problem":"COLOREC","solution":"http://dataurbia.com/16nV","link":"http://dataurbia.com/16oZ"},
    {"problem":"DHEXP","solution":"http://dataurbia.com/15oD","link":"http://dataurbia.com/15m3"},
    {"problem":"DQUERY","solution":"http://dataurbia.com/12ZO","link":"http://dataurbia.com/12Yx"},
    {"problem":"HEAP1","solution":"http://dataurbia.com/zVX","link":"http://dataurbia.com/zUR"},
    {"problem":"KBUILD","solution":"http://dataurbia.com/16bD","link":"http://dataurbia.com/16bW"},
    {"problem":"LQDGONME","solution":"http://dataurbia.com/zd4","link":"http://dataurbia.com/yUI"},
    {"problem":"MATSUM","solution":"http://dataurbia.com/1ADj","link":"http://dataurbia.com/1ABu"},
    {"problem":"MEDIAN","solution":"http://dataurbia.com/18Wu","link":"http://dataurbia.com/18YJ"},
    {"problem":"NKCITY","solution":"http://dataurbia.com/1245","link":"http://dataurbia.com/120Q"},
    {"problem":"NKMAXSEQ","solution":"http://dataurbia.com/uFR","link":"http://dataurbia.com/tax"},
    {"problem":"QMAX","solution":"http://dataurbia.com/zzQ","link":"http://dataurbia.com/zrZ"},
    {"problem":"QMAX2","solution":"http://dataurbia.com/10AY","link":"http://dataurbia.com/104N"},
    {"problem":"SPSEQ","solution":"http://dataurbia.com/pXd","link":"http://dataurbia.com/pKp"},
    {"problem":"V8ORG","solution":"http://dataurbia.com/12iA","link":"http://dataurbia.com/12YN"},
    {"problem":"AMSSEQ","solution":"http://viahold.com/Bdp","link":"http://ideone.com/PqORE8"},
    {"problem":"JOBSET","solution":"http://viahold.com/BW4","link":"http://viahold.com/BOl"},
    {"problem":"KQUERY2","solution":"http://viahold.com/4Ne","link":"http://viahold.com/4C9"},
    {"problem":"MINCUT","solution":"http://viahold.com/6Zj","link":"http://viahold.com/6fG"},
    {"problem":"VO17LAN","solution":"http://viahold.com/AEU","link":"http://viahold.com/AGB"},
    {"problem":"VO17PHD","solution":"http://viahold.com/AuH","link":"http://viahold.com/AcA"},
    {"problem":"BINARY2","solution":"http://viahold.com/YWF","link":"http://viahold.com/YZS"},
    {"problem":"BASEH","solution":"http://viahold.com/YJi","link":"http://viahold.com/YKY"},
    {"problem":"BLGEN","solution":"http://viahold.com/YuJ","link":"http://viahold.com/Yud"},
    {"problem":"C11PNUM","solution":"http://viahold.com/YcH","link":"http://viahold.com/Ycx"},
    {"problem":"FLOW1","solution":"http://viahold.com/YzF","link":"http://viahold.com/YmZ"},
    {"problem":"LEM7","solution":"http://viahold.com/X2z","link":"http://viahold.com/X43"},
    {"problem":"MINK","solution":"http://viahold.com/SaT","link":"http://viahold.com/SZm"},
    {"problem":"MTOTALF","solution":"http://viahold.com/Nn8","link":"http://viahold.com/Nnh"},
    {"problem":"NKFLOW","solution":"http://viahold.com/Nbk","link":"http://ideone.com/DGrZT7"},
    {"problem":"PALINY","solution":"http://viahold.com/NCj","link":"http://viahold.com/NHI"},
    {"problem":"QTDIVSEQ","solution":"http://viahold.com/ROl","link":"http://viahold.com/S0J"},
    {"problem":"C11CAVE","solution":"http://viahold.com/mwW","link":"http://viahold.com/mtJ"},
    {"problem":"CHEER","solution":"http://viahold.com/n0j","link":"http://viahold.com/n14"},
    {"problem":"NKDIVSEQ","solution":"http://viahold.com/pic","link":"http://viahold.com/piw"},
    {"problem":"SEQ198","solution":"http://viahold.com/oUJ","link":"http://viahold.com/oU0"},
    {"problem":"BONES","solution":"http://viahold.com/1CRK","link":"http://viahold.com/1CSS"},
    {"problem":"C11BC1","solution":"http://viahold.com/1D4C","link":"http://viahold.com/1CWh"},
    {"problem":"C11DK1","solution":"http://viahold.com/1DPo","link":"http://viahold.com/1DQZ"},
    {"problem":"C11SUM","solution":"http://viahold.com/1EEP","link":"http://viahold.com/1EFW"},
    {"problem":"KSEQ1","solution":"http://viahold.com/13wy","link":"http://viahold.com/13x5"},
    {"problem":"MESSAGE","solution":"http://viahold.com/1E5m","link":"http://viahold.com/1E0W"},
    {"problem":"NKREZ","solution":"http://viahold.com/17Am","link":"http://viahold.com/178O"},
    {"problem":"VMQUABEO","solution":"http://viahold.com/1DnO","link":"http://viahold.com/1Do1"},
    {"problem":"VOGAME","solution":"http://viahold.com/1DkR","link":"http://viahold.com/1DSg"},
    {"problem":"VOSCUN","solution":"http://viahold.com/1Et7","link":"http://viahold.com/1EfK"},
    {"problem":"VOSMAXK","solution":"http://viahold.com/1EPX","link":"http://viahold.com/1EDi"},
    {"problem":"ACQUIRE","solution":"http://viahold.com/1V3Z","link":"http://viahold.com/1V48"},
    {"problem":"AREA","solution":"http://viahold.com/1OtE","link":"http://viahold.com/1Orx"},
    {"problem":"C11ID","solution":"http://viahold.com/1Xd7","link":"http://viahold.com/1XeB"},
    {"problem":"CRATE","solution":"http://viahold.com/1QpE","link":"http://viahold.com/1QeA"},
    {"problem":"KGSS","solution":"http://viahold.com/1T8P","link":"http://viahold.com/1T8q"},
    {"problem":"MBEEWALK","solution":"http://viahold.com/1Xdu","link":"http://viahold.com/1XcT"},
    {"problem":"MDOLLS","solution":"http://viahold.com/1RRR","link":"http://viahold.com/1ROJ"},
    {"problem":"MSTRING","solution":"http://viahold.com/1Xew","link":"http://viahold.com/1XTW"},
    {"problem":"NKINV","solution":"http://viahold.com/1XHB","link":"http://viahold.com/1X4L"},
    {"problem":"NKLEAGUE","solution":"http://viahold.com/1QQK","link":"http://viahold.com/1QQf"},
    {"problem":"NKLUCK","solution":"http://viahold.com/1Ye1","link":"http://viahold.com/1Y5Y"},
    {"problem":"NKNUMFRE","solution":"http://viahold.com/1YpN","link":"http://viahold.com/1Yno"},
    {"problem":"QBSEGPAR","solution":"http://viahold.com/1S0g","link":"http://viahold.com/1S1A"},
    {"problem":"ROADS","solution":"http://viahold.com/1t7x","link":"http://viahold.com/1Z4I"},
    {"problem":"ROBOCON","solution":"http://viahold.com/1PXo","link":"http://viahold.com/1PZ2"},
    {"problem":"SOPENP","solution":"http://viahold.com/1XTP","link":"http://viahold.com/1X85"},
    {"problem":"VMSORT","solution":"http://viahold.com/1Q1e","link":"http://viahold.com/1Q2G"},
    {"problem":"VMTRIP","solution":"http://viahold.com/1SJF","link":"http://viahold.com/1SJV"},
    {"problem":"VMUNCH","solution":"http://viahold.com/1TQx","link":"http://viahold.com/1TOv"},
    {"problem":"VO17SORT","solution":"http://viahold.com/1Wwj","link":"http://viahold.com/1Wqh"},
    {"problem":"VOXOR","solution":"http://viahold.com/1Pt2","link":"http://viahold.com/1Ptx"},
    {"problem":"QTREE3","solution":"http://viahold.com/1mJA","link":"http://viahold.com/1mJm"},
    {"problem":"APIO10A","solution":"http://viahold.com/1uCj","link":"http://viahold.com/1tt2"},
    {"problem":"NK05MNIM","solution":"http://viahold.com/1ugl","link":"http://viahold.com/1uSb"},
    {"problem":"PVOI14_3","solution":"http://viahold.com/2H51","link":"http://viahold.com/2Gek"},
    {"problem":"BAOVE","solution":"http://viahold.com/2y8W","link":"http://viahold.com/2y6u"},
    {"problem":"BALLGMVN","solution":"http://viahold.com/3a1P","link":"http://viahold.com/3a0b"},
    {"problem":"TFIELD","solution":"http://viahold.com/3VrS","link":"http://viahold.com/3Vrm"},
    {"problem":"VMPIZZA","solution":"http://viahold.com/3ekA","link":"http://viahold.com/3eno"},
    {"problem":"BYTESH1","solution":"http://kaitect.com/53C","link":"http://kaitect.com/54H"},
    {"problem":"COMPUTER","solution":"http://yobuilder.com/8Yjv","link":"http://yobuilder.com/8YmM"},
    {"problem":"VOSNET","solution":"http://twineer.com/1IbA","link":"http://twineer.com/1I8v"},
    {"problem":"TRAKA","solution":"http://vializer.com/1MsR","link":"http://vializer.com/1K5j"}]